(Raj:)If you're really
Nathan Fillion,
what's the line from Firefly
about your bonnet?
"I swear by my pretty floral
bonnet, I will end you."
(Penny:)That's it,
that's the line.
(Raj:)Although...
(Raj:)I knew the line--
doesn't make me Nathan Fillion.
(Nathan Fillion:)Do you want the picture or not?
(Raj:)I want a picture
with Nathan Fillion.
(Nathan:)How about a picture with a guy
who looks like Nathan Fillion
(Nathan:)but a little more annoyed
than Nathan Fillion usually is?
(Leonard:)What do you think?
Eh, it's good enough
for Facebook.
(Penny:)I can't believe
they did that.
(Penny:)I know-- it's so insulting.
(Penny:)At one point,
they had me figure out
(Penny:)how to get a banana
out of a puzzle box.
(Leonard:)Wait, Sheldon gave me
a banana in a box.
(Leonard:)He was testing me, too.
(Penny:)Unbelievable.